All New Dragons
Book of Dragons is a fantasy, animation, action film directed by Steve Hickner.
So you want to be a dragon trainer do you?
Prepare yourself for adventure, excitement and training as Hiccup, Astrid, Toothless and Gobber tell the legend
behind the Book of Dragons and reveal insider training secrets about new, never-before-seen dragons.
Hiccup (voice), played by Jay Baruchel.
Gobber (voice), played by Craig Ferguson.
Astrid (voice), played by America Ferrera.
Fishlegs (voice), played by Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
Bork (voice), played by Jim Cummings.
Bork's Wife (voice), played by Tress MacNeille.
Dragon (Chinese: 武俠; pinyin: Wǔ xiá) is a 2011 martial arts film directed by
Peter Chan, and starring Donnie Yen, Takeshi Kaneshiro and Tang Wei.
In this Hong Kong-Chinese co-production, Yen also
served as the film's action director.
It premiered on 13 May 2011 at the 2011 Cannes Film
Festival in the Midnight Screenings category.
Donnie Yen and Peter Chan presided over the lighting of a 3591-square-metre billboard for Dragon that broke the record in the
Guinness Book of World Records for its size, a record previously held by a poster for a Michael Jackson album.
The tone is lighthearted.